<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel Guide1.0</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="title_activity_smaps">activity_smaps</string>
    <item name="location_name" type="id" />
    <string name="title_activity_adwela_map">AdwelaMapActivity</string>
    <string name="a_waterfall_is_any_point_in_a_river_or_stream_where_water_flows_over_a_vertical_drop_or_a_series_of_steep_drops_waterfalls_also_occur_where_meltwater_drops_over_the_edge_of_a_tabular_iceberg_or_ice_shelf_nwaterfalls_can_be_formed_in_several_ways_but_the_most_common_method_of_formation_is_that_a_river_courses_over_a_top_layer_of_resistant_bedrock_before_falling_on_to_softer_rock_which_erodes_faster_leading_to_an_increasingly_high_fall_waterfalls_have_been_studied_for_their_impact_on_species_living_in_and_around_them_nhumans_have_had_a_distinct_relationship_with_waterfalls_for_years_travelling_to_see_them_exploring_and_naming_them_they_can_present_formidable_barriers_to_navigation_along_rivers_waterfalls_are_religious_sites_in_many_cultures_since_the_18th_century_they_have_received_increased_attention_as_tourist_destinations_sources_of_hydropower_and_particularly_since_the_mid_20th_century_as_subjects_of_research">A waterfall is any point in a river or stream where water flows over a vertical drop or a series of steep drops. Waterfalls also occur where meltwater drops over the edge of a tabular iceberg or ice shelf. \nWaterfalls can be formed in several ways, but the most common method of formation is that a river courses over a top layer of resistant bedrock before falling on to softer rock, which erodes faster, leading to an increasingly high fall. Waterfalls have been studied for their impact on species living in and around them. \nHumans have had a distinct relationship with waterfalls for years, travelling to see them, exploring and naming them. They can present formidable barriers to navigation along rivers. Waterfalls are religious sites in many cultures. Since the 18th century they have received increased attention as tourist destinations, sources of hydropower, and—particularly since the mid-20th century—as subjects of research.</string>
    <string name="Travel_description">\nEmbark on an enchanting journey through India\'s captivating landscapes and cultural wonders. Marvel at the architectural brilliance of the iconic Taj Mahal in Agra, delve into the spiritual aura of Varanasi along the Ganges, and immerse yourself in the royal history of Jaipur with its palaces and forts.\n\nVenture into the Himalayan region, where the scenic beauty of Manali, Shimla, and Leh-Ladakh unfolds, offering not just panoramic vistas but also opportunities for adventure and exploration. Discover the diverse wildlife in the Ranthambore and Jim Corbett National Parks, where the majestic Bengal tiger reigns supreme.\n\nRelax on the sun-kissed beaches of Goa, known for its vibrant nightlife and Portuguese-influenced architecture, or cruise through the tranquil backwaters of Kerala on traditional houseboats surrounded by lush greenery. Experience the unique cultural heritage of Mysore\'s opulent palace in Karnataka and witness the ancient artistry at the Ajanta and Ellora Caves in Maharashtra.\n\nFeel the spiritual resonance at the Golden Temple in Amritsar, a serene oasis amidst bustling surroundings, and explore the pristine white sandy beaches of the Andaman and Nicobar Islands. Dive into the cultural extravaganza of the Pushkar Camel Fair in Rajasthan, a vibrant celebration that captures the essence of traditional Indian festivities.\n\nIndia, with its kaleidoscope of travel attractions, promises an immersive blend of history, spirituality, natural beauty, and adventure, making it an unparalleled destination for the discerning traveler.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Top_10_places">\n 1. Taj Mahal, Agra \n 2. Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh \n 3. Jaipur, Rajasthan \n 4. Himalayan (Leh-Ladakh) \n 5. Kerala Backwaters \n 6. Mysore, Karnataka \n 7. Ahmedabad \n 8. Ajanta and Ellora Caves, Maharashtra \n 9. Golden Temple, Amritsar, Punjab \n 10. Goa</string>
    <string name="nthere_are_9_province_in_india_n_n">\nThere are 9 Province in India\n\n</string>
    <string name="taj_mahal_des">Mausoleum: Explore the intricate white marble structure, adorned with calligraphy and floral motifs, housing the cenotaphs of Shah Jahan and Mumtaz Mahal. \n\nGardens and Pool: Wander through well-maintained gardens, pathways, and a reflecting pool surrounding the Taj Mahal, capturing stunning reflections during sunrise or sunset.  \n\nViewpoints: Discover different angles for capturing the grandeur of the Taj Mahal, including the Yamuna River and Mehtab Bagh for unique perspectives and sunset views</string>
    <string name="varanasi_des">Ganges Ghats: Experience spiritual rituals and boat rides at Ganges River ghats, especially Dashashwamedh Ghat.  \n\nKashi Vishwanath Temple: Holiest Hindu temple dedicated to Lord Shiva, known for intricate architecture and religious significance.  \n\nSarnath: Ancient site where Buddha gave his first sermon, featuring Dhamek Stupa and an Archaeological Museum.</string>
    <string name="jaipur_des">Hawa Mahal (Palace of Winds): Visit this iconic palace known for its unique architecture with numerous small windows, allowing the royal ladies to observe street festivities without being seen. Explore its five floors and enjoy panoramic views of Jaipur. \n\nCity Palace: Immerse yourself in the rich history of Jaipur by exploring the City Palace, a complex of courtyards, gardens, and buildings. Visit the museum to see artifacts, textiles, and art reflecting the royal heritage of the region.\n\nAmber Fort: Venture to the outskirts of Jaipur to experience the grandeur of Amber Fort. Explore the intricate architecture, including the Sheesh Mahal (Mirror Palace) and enjoy an elephant ride up to the fort. Marvel at the stunning views of the surrounding hills and Maota Lake.</string>
    <string name="ladakh_des">Pangong Lake: Experience the mesmerizing beauty of this high-altitude lake with ever-changing hues and stunning mountain reflections.\n\nNubra Valley: Explore the cold desert landscape, ride camels in the sand dunes, and visit the Diskit Monastery.\n\nLeh Palace: Discover the historic Leh Palace, offering panoramic views of the Leh town and the surrounding Himalayan mountains.</string>
    <string name="amdavad_pkg_txt">Kankaria Lake: Unwind at Kankaria Lake, a bustling waterfront with a leisure park, boat rides, and an evening light show, making it a popular spot for both locals and tourists.\n\nAkshardham Temple: Marvel at the impressive Akshardham Temple, an intricately carved Hindu temple dedicated to Lord Swaminarayan, featuring stunning architecture, lush gardens, and a cultural complex.\n\nAdalaj Stepwell: Step into the architectural beauty of Adalaj Stepwell, an intricately designed stepwell with stunning carvings, providing both a functional and aesthetic marvel.\n\nCalico Museum of Textiles: Immerse yourself in the rich textile heritage of India at the Calico Museum of Textiles, displaying a vast collection of fabrics, artifacts, and exhibits.  Science City: Engage in interactive learning and entertainment at Science City, an educational complex with exhibits, a planetarium, and an IMAX theater, making it a great destination for families.</string>
    <string name="kerela_pkg_txt">Backwaters of Alleppey: Cruise through the picturesque backwaters of Alleppey on a traditional houseboat, surrounded by lush greenery and tranquil waters.\n\nPeriyar National Park: Embark on a wildlife adventure at Periyar National Park, home to diverse flora and fauna, and enjoy a boat ride on Periyar Lake.\n\nMunnar Tea Gardens: Explore the sprawling tea plantations of Munnar, set against the backdrop of rolling hills, and witness the tea-making process in the lush landscapes.</string>
    <string name="mysore_pkg_txt">Chamundi Hills: Ascend the Chamundi Hills to visit the Chamundeshwari Temple, offering panoramic views of Mysore, and witness the colossal Nandi statue carved out of a single rock.\n\nBrindavan Gardens: Explore the enchanting Brindavan Gardens, famous for its musical fountain that comes alive with colorful lights and synchronized music in the evenings.  \n\nJaganmohan Palace Art Gallery: Immerse yourself in the rich cultural heritage at Jaganmohan Palace Art Gallery, home to an impressive collection of paintings, sculptures, and artifacts.</string>
    <string name="mumbai_txt">Gateway of India: Begin your Mumbai exploration at the iconic Gateway of India, a historic monument overlooking the Arabian Sea, with intricate architecture and a bustling waterfront.\n\nChhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus: Marvel at the UNESCO World Heritage Site, Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus, a magnificent railway station featuring Victorian Gothic architecture and stunning details.  \n\nMarine Drive: Enjoy a leisurely stroll along Marine Drive, also known as the Queen\'s Necklace, with a mesmerizing view of the Arabian Sea and the city skyline.\n\nElephanta Caves: Take a boat ride to Elephanta Island and explore the ancient Elephanta Caves, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, housing intricate sculptures and rock-cut temples dedicated to Lord Shiva.  \n\nColaba Causeway: Experience the vibrant atmosphere of Colaba Causeway, a bustling street market offering a diverse range of shops, street food, and cultural experiences.</string>
    <string name="goa_txt">Basilica of Bom Jesus: Explore the UNESCO World Heritage Site, Basilica of Bom Jesus, a 16th-century church in Old Goa containing the mortal remains of St. Francis Xavier.  \n\nBeaches of North Goa: Immerse yourself in the vibrant atmosphere of popular beaches like Baga, Calangute, and Anjuna, known for their golden sands, water sports, and lively shacks.  \n\nDudhsagar Waterfalls: Experience the breathtaking Dudhsagar Waterfalls, one of India\'s tallest waterfalls, surrounded by lush greenery and accessible by trekking or jeep safari.  \n\nFort Aguada: Visit Fort Aguada, a well-preserved 17th-century Portuguese fort with panoramic views of the Arabian Sea, featuring a lighthouse and historical significance.  \n\nAnjuna Flea Market: Explore the vibrant Anjuna Flea Market, a haven for shoppers offering a plethora of goods, from souvenirs and clothing to local handicrafts and jewelry.  \n\nChapora Fort: Enjoy the picturesque views from Chapora Fort, a historic fortress overlooking the Arabian Sea, famous for its appearance in the Bollywood movie Dil Chahta Hai.</string>
</resources>